Contact

6303038303 (Mobile) sairithvikkanakamedala@gmai I.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rithvik7 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Assembly Language
C

Certifications

Al for Medical Diagnosis
Neural Networks and Deep Learning
Structuring Machine Learning
Projects

Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyperparameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization Machine Learning by Andrew NG

Sai Rithvik Kanakamedala

Data Science, Deep Learning Enthusiast | Al Researcher at HaleAl Hyderabad

Summary

Artificial Intelligence Researcher with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Machine Learning Algorithms, Deep Learning, Python and C Language. Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in Electrical and Electronics Engineering from Indian Institute of Technology, Madras.

Though coming from a "Non- Computer Science" field, the impact that AI can create has constantly motivated me in learning the state of the the art methods in AI. Have experience in working on various Data handling and Visualization Projects in Python. Looking forward to apply my knowledge in the real world problems which will help the world in a better way.

Experience

HaleAl 5 months

Artificial Intelligence Researcher July 2020 - Present (2 months) Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Artificial Intelligence Research Intern April 2020 - June 2020 (3 months) Hyderabad, Telangana

Education

Indian Institute of Technology, Madras
Bachelor's degree, Electrical and Electronics Engineering (2018 - 2022)